{
    "subject": "resource/New_York_Yankees",
    "predicate": "property/misc",
    "object": "Based in New York since 1903",
    "human_readable": "The New York Yankees are based in New York since 1903.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9231473803520203,
            "question": "What team is known for being based in New York since 1903?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8784364461898804,
            "question": "Where are the New York Yankees based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7772678136825562,
            "question": "How long have the New York Yankees been based in New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.754479169845581,
            "question": "What year did the New York Yankees begin playing in New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6932211518287659,
            "question": "Since when have the New York Yankees called New York their home?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6803531050682068,
            "question": "What year marks the beginning of the New York Yankees' presence in New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6754046082496643,
            "question": "Is the New York Yankees team currently located in New York?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5766971707344055,
            "question": "In what city do the New York Yankees reside?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.402387410402298,
            "question": "Name the location of the New York Yankees' home base."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39670950174331665,
            "question": "Which city is home to the New York Yankees?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The New York Yankees are based in New York since 1903.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5138_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the location of the New York Yankees' home base.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5138_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what city do the New York Yankees reside?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5138_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is the New York Yankees team currently located in New York?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5138_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5138_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: All the provided documents indicate that the New York Yankees moved to and have been based in the Bronx, New York City, since their inception in 1903. Therefore, the statement \"The New York Yankees are based in New York since 1903\" is supported by the given information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}